dotv.com 2009-04-25

# DoTV.com PRIVACY POLICY

**DoTV.com PRIVACY POLICY**

DoTV.com, a service provided by PPM Technology Group, Inc., (PPM) understands that your privacy is very important to you. That's why we've developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is protected while using DoTV.com. 

### Table of Contents

  * A Special Note About Children
  * Information Broadcast By You
  * About DoTV.com and Information We Collect
  * Our Use of Your Information
  * Our Disclosure of Your Information
  * Your use of Other Users' Information
  * Control of Your Password
  * Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information
  * Third Party Collections of Information
  * Security
  * Update/Delete
  * Changes to This Policy

### 1\. A Special Note About Children

Persons under 18 are not eligible to use our services. If you are under 18, we ask that you do not submit information to us. 

### 2\. Information Broadcast By You

DoTV.coms potential audience includes anyone with internet access. If you choose to post, speak, broadcast or otherwise disseminate any personal information ( broadcast information ) about yourself, you should understand that you have potentially made this information publicly available and no longer have any expectation of privacy (with respect to the broadcast information). If you want to keep personal information private, please do not broadcast it. 

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should also be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Once posted, you cannot change or remove any public postings made in our chat rooms or other message areas. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. We also reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our [Terms of Use](http://dotv.com/go/page/terms_of_use.html). 

### 3\. About DoTV.com and Information We Collect

DoTV.com is an online webcasting social network that provides you with useful tools to build social networks online. DoTV.coms basic service is FREE to all qualified members. 

During our registration process, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information, such as your birth date, email address, etc. In addition, to enable certain paid features on our website, we also collect your street address, credit card, and/or bank information. (Persons who reside in the United States and earn more than $600 per calendar year must provide specific information so that we can send you a 1099.) This information can be accessed or used by individuals under the supervision of PPM and is not available to the public except as noted below. 

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses and email addresses. Many sites collect this sort of information. We may tie your IP address to your personally identifiable information. If you choose to post messages, profiles or videos in various areas of our website, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file, which is only accessed by authorized personnel. We may also collect other users' comments about you in our complaints department. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friends name and email address. We may automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. DoTV.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at Customer Service to request that we remove this information from our database. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies. A session ID cookie simply terminates once a user closes the browser. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

### 4\. Our Use of Your Information

We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to process member payment and monetary transactions, to comply with applicable law, to combat abuse or violation of our [Terms of Use](http://dotv.com/go/page/terms_of_use.html) and to improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor your online experience to meet your needs. We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Term of Use. 

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. 

We send periodic informational updates to our members via email. We send e-mail advertisements to those who opted in to receive such advertisements or otherwise in compliance with the Can-Spam statute. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our updates and communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in the email or email us at Customer Service. We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the Personal Preferences Page or you may contact us at DoTV.com, Attn: Customer Service, 220 Humboldt Ct,  
Sunnyvale, CA 94089, to opt-out. 

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice prominently on our site. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

### 5\. Our Disclosure of Your Information

We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third-party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed in aggregate at all. 

In order to maintain a healthy community, DoTV.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights (including combating abuse or violations or our [Terms of Use](http://dotv.com/go/page/terms_of_use.html)) and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We use a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

### 6\. Your use of Other Users' Information

You may not use other users information for commercial purposes, to spam, to harass, or to make unlawful threats. DoTV.com reserves the right to terminate those who misuse other users information or who otherwise violate the DoTV.com Terms of Use. 

### 7\. Control of Your Password

You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. 

### 8\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

Once you register, you will be able to review and change much of your personally identifiable information at DoTV.com including: 

  * Your email address
  * Your city, state, zip code, country
  * Your password
  * Your profile

Please promptly update your information if it changes by logging in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly urge you to periodically change your password to help reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your account information. 

Upon your request, we will remove your credit card number and credit card expiration date from our main databases. To make this request, email us at Customer Service. We will retain in our files information, including credit card information, you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, comply with Credit Card Merchant Banking and Association Agreements, enhance security, reduce fraud, comply with Federal and State Law, and to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement. 

### 9\. Third Party Collections of Information

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties on our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. While DoTV.com is working closely with our partners to ensure the highest privacy to you, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click here. 

### 10\. Security

DoTV.com has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, please contact us. 

### 11\. Update/Delete

DoTV.com Members have the following choices to modify or delete their information from our database: 

  * Send an email to Customer Service;
  * Log in with your password and modify/delete your profile;
  * Send a snail mail to DoTV.com, Att: Customer Service, 220 Humboldt Ct,  
Sunnyvale, CA 94089;

Click here to join our free, safe, and exciting community now. 

### 12\. Changes to This Policy

Changes to our privacy policy will be posted in this privacy statement, and may be posted on the homepage, or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

DoTV.com PRIVACY POLICY Effective on: (12/15/06)
